The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
♪ Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano ♪
The dreams I see are my secret
♪ Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano ♪
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
♪ Akai manto hira hira ♪
A red cape fluttering
♪ Uma o tobasu oujo ♪
Galloping on a horse—the princess
♪ Sore ga atashi ♪
That’s me!
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Ribon no kishi wa ♪
The Knight of the Ribbon,
♪ Honto wa hontto wa ♪
Truly, truly,
♪ Atashi nano sa ♪
It’s really me!
Forty-Ninth Episode
Lord X
Hecate's Smile
The X-Union.
Its forces have finally approached the border of Silverland.
The massive X-Union army has destroyed Demon Mountain in its path,
and now nothing stands between them and the invasion of Silverland.
Commander Ghana, sir!
Commander a message from headquarters!
We are ordered to conquer Demon Mountain before the main force arrives.
All right, good work!
Demon Mountain?
Move out!
Fire!
Onward! Charge!
Glad you could make it, Hecate.
Sapphire, why are you practicing with bows and spears?
Because the X-Union is going to attack Silverland,
so I have to protect my kingdom.
I guess there are bad humans too.
Yeah, that's right.
But humans can care for each other and fall in love, right?
That's true.
Humans are wonderful, aren't they?
Yeah.
Hecate, there's nothing wrong with you falling in love with a human, either.
To fall in love with a human...
Lord Sapphire, it is time for the meeting.
Is it that time already?
Well, see you later, Sapphire.
All right, let's meet in the forest by the mountain in one week.
All right.
Hecate, you be careful of the X-Union too, okay?
Yeah, you too, Sapphire.
Sapphire told me that even I could fall in love.
La la la
La la la la
La la
Hecate!
Oh,
Papa, Mama!
Hecate, what are you thinking?
Hecate, it's no use hiding it.
I can see right through your heart.
You're trying to fall in love with a human.
Huh?
No, Mama...
Don't lie.
You're a demon's daughter.
If you fall in love with a human,
the Great Demon King will punish you terribly.
Mama, tell Hecate how terrifying the Great Demon King's punishment is.
What's the Great Demon King's punishment?
The punishment the Great Demon King inflicts on us is truly terrifying.
Got that, Hecate?
Don't disobey your parents.
All right, Papa, Mama.
All right, then.
We're off to the Demon Convention.
Hey, wait a minute.
Hurry up, or we'll be late.
Take this snake charm with you so I'll know if anything happens to you.
It's set up to alert me right away if something goes wrong.
Off you go, Papa! Mama!
Commander! The demons have left!
Right! Bring down that mountain! Ready to fire!
Hecate,
you are a demon's daughter.
If you fall in love with a human,
the Great Demon King will punish you horribly.
Oh, but Mama...
Fire! Keep firing!
Help me! Papa! Mama!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Destroy Demon Mountain!
It's a demon's daughter!
A demon!
Prepare yourself, demon!
You're a witch, so you're going to burn at the stake!
Or do you want to fight?!
Help me!
Prepare yourself!
Wait!
What are you doing?
Let her go!
But Commander,
she's a witch!
Witch or not,
she's just a girl!
What about, the invasion?
We must consult Lord X first.
Leave this to me for now.
Hey, miss, show me your arm.
Are you all right?
Someone fetch the medical kit!
It'll turn bad if we leave it like this.
Prepare a horse for her.
Now, miss, I must take you to Lord X.
Come with us quietly.
Got it?
Yes.
Miss, what is your name?
My name is Hecate.
Hecate...
That's a nice name.
And you?
Me? I'm Ghana.
Let's go!
Forward!
Something must have happened to Hecate!
My charm broke, after all.
I certainly hope not...
It's gone! Our house is gone!
Hecate!
Could she have been kidnapped by someone?
There are tracks from a large group passing through.
All right, let's go after them!
There it is! Hecate is there, too!
All right, just you wait!
A demon! A demon! This is a demon's work!
Did you see my power?
If you don't return my beloved daughter Hecate...
I'll make you suffer even more!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Ah, Mephisto, was it? Thank you for coming.
Who are you?!
I am X, a human demon.
Like you, I seek to build a world of evil on Earth.
A world of evil?
Indeed, Mephisto.
We shall bring this world under evil's rule.
Starting with Silverland.
What do you say, Mephisto?
Why not join forces with me?
How fascinating. If you're serious, I'd be happy to help.
We'll gladly lend you our aid. But first...
yes, first we want our daughter Hecate returned.
Very well, I'll return her.
Provided you fulfill my condition...
A condition!?
Capture Princess Sapphire of Silverland,
and I will give back your daughter.
Hello there, little birds. How are you?
I'm supposed to meet Hecate here today, little birds.
But she's late. It's way past the time we agreed on.
What's wrong?
What's that?
Sapphire! We're in luck finding you in a place like this.
You demons!
Zubarosha!
Where on earth am I...?
That's right!
Mephisto captured me and brought me to this X-Union tent.
I have to find a way to escape!
If we let Sapphire escape, Lord X will have our heads!
You've done well, Mephisto.
X, now that we have captured Sapphire,
Silverland is practically ours for the taking.
Indeed, it is all thanks to you and your group.
Sapphire...
I have to save Sapphire...
That must be the tent where Sapphire is being held.
Wait... it's you!
What are you doing here, Hecate?
You were watching Sapphire's tent.
Please, help Sapphire. She's my friend.
Hecate, I... No, I can't possibly do that.
Ghana, even if the person giving you orders is evil...
Fine then, Ghana. I'll save Sapphire myself.
Hecate!
What a troublesome girl. Stay here.
Save the talk for outside, hurry!
Hecate, hurry!
It's Sapphire! Sapphire has escaped!
Hold it!
This is bad! At this rate, all three of us will get caught!
Stop right there!
All right!
Come on! You're not getting past me!
What?!
You traitor!
Hecate, run!
Sapphire, we'll be safe once we reach the Black Forest.
I wonder if Ghana is okay.
What?
Ghana let Sapphire escape?!
What are you all dawdling for?
Go catch Sapphire!
X, panicking won't help you catch Sapphire now.
Lord X, that demon's daughter over there helped Sapphire escape too.
What? What did you say?
Where's Hecate?
Mephisto, it seems your daughter put Ghana up to this.
This is a bad situation, Mephisto.
All right, I have a plan. Lend me Ghana downstairs.
I'll bring Sapphire back for sure.
And we'll handle this alone, so promise you won't get in our way.
Very well. Take Ghana with you.
I certainly promise you, X.
I wonder if Sapphire and Hecate will come here.
Don't worry. If we take Ghana there,
soft-hearted Sapphire and Hecate are sure to show up.
Zubarasha!
Eraisha!
Now Sapphire and Hecate will know Ghana is here.
Why would you start a fire...?
Look at that.
My magical fog and fire project Ghana's giant form into the night sky.
Oh, look, Sapphire! Ghana! It's Ghana!
Ghana! Ghana!
Ghana, so you really were captured after all.
Hecate,
you like that commander,
don't you?
Yeah...
But didn't I tell you before that even a demon can fall in love with a human?
Anyway, it seems Ghana is beyond that mountain. Let's hurry, Hecate.
They're here.
Those footsteps must be Hecate and Sapphire.
Let's wait and see what Hecate does.
All right.
Ghana!
Ghana, I'm coming!
Ghana! Ghana!
Hecate!
You're awake, Ghana.
Hecate, stay back! It's dangerous! It's a trap! Run, hurry!
What are you saying, Ghana? I'm going to save you.
Hang in there, Hecate! Just a little more!
Hecate.
Mephisto!
Hecate, what are you doing?!
After everything I told you! Come down right now!
Papa, Mama!
Come on, Hecate. Come down quickly.
Don't you listen to us?!
Hecate.
That's right, Hecate. Hurry and get down! Forget about me!
Ghana, I can't just forget you!
I can't, Papa, Mama!
What?
I'm sorry, Papa, Mama.
I'm going to save Ghana!
Hecate, you haven't forgotten what happens
if you fall in love with a human, have you?!
Hecate, Papa made a deal with X! Hurry up and come down!
A deal with X?
What? Mephisto! X isn't the kind of man to keep a promise! Look at that!
It's about time. Are you ready to attack?
Do it!
Damn it! Hey! That bastard X!
Hecate! We have to get Ghana down, quick!
Hecate! Hurry, hurry! It's dangerous!
Hecate! Are you all right?
Hang in there, Ghana! Just a little more!
Hecate, it won't untie!
What are you doing, Hecate?!
It's dangerous! Get down, quick!
More cannonballs are coming!
Get down, Hecate!
Curse that hateful X!
Now I'll blow you away!
Traitors, watch this!
Matte Mephisto!
- Stop Mephisto!
Omae ga X o yattsuketara,
- If you defeat X,
ningen o aishita Hecate no mikata o shita koto ni naru zo
- it means you've taken the side of Hecate, who loves a human!
Omae ga X o yattsukereba, washi no batsu o ukeneba naran.
- If you defeat X, you must face my punishment.
Soredemo yoi no ka?
- Are you truly prepared for that?
Omaetachi wa X no mikata o suru nda!
- You will side with X!
Come on, hurry, Ghana!
Thank goodness, Ghana.
Thank you. Is Hecate okay?
Thank goodness!
Hecate!
Don't die! Hecate! Hecate! Don't die!
Damn it! Curse you, X!
Impudent humans!
You won't get away with mocking a demon!
Behold my final magic!
Zubarasha!
Papa!
Wow, well done!
Hecate, watch your mama's magic carefully!
Mama!
Mizu yo! Mizu yo! Sakamake! Uzumake!
- Water! Water! Surge! Swirl!
Zubarasha!
What foolish demons, sacrificing their own lives.
We must retreat for now.
Noroware! Dai-mao no okite o yabutta oroka na yatsura!
- Be cursed, you fools who broke the Great Demon King's law!
Dai-mao no batsu to shite—Mephisto...!
- As punishment from the Great Demon King—Mephisto...!
Omae wa yama!
- You shall become a mountain!
Hell,
Omae wa mizumi!
- you shall become a lake!
Eikyu ni moto no akuma ni modorenai yo ni shite yaru!
- You will never return to your demonic forms!
Hecate yo
- Hecate,
omae ni mo nido to akuma ni modorenai batsu o kurete yaru!
- I shall punish you too so you can never be a demon again!
Omae wa toki ga tateba shinde shimau,
- You shall become a pitiful human
aware na ningen ni naru no da!
- who will grow old and die!
Papa!
Mama!
Hecate, your Papa and Mama cast that rainbow wishing for your happiness.
They are saying...
Go into the human world and be happy with Ghana.
Ghana!
Hecate!
Come on, shall we go?
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen ♪
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
♪ Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen ♪
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
♪ Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo ♪
Even if demons come, even if storms arrive,
♪ tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai ♪
Our bonded hearts will never part.
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP